Guide to the Theodore Dorie Friend Collection, 1897-1990
Friend, Theodore Dorie Collection
- Series X: Microforms, Disks, transparencies
  - Microfilm- Japanese Army and Navy, Rules and Reg, Pris of War, 9-5-43 (Box 19)
  - Microfilm- Japanese Army and Navy, Gen Reports, Jan-Sept ’42; Mil Govt, Microfilm- P.I. esp. Watari group (Box 19)
  - Microfilm- Japanese Army and Navy, Intelligence Reports on various places, including Philippines, 1933 (Box 19)
  - Microfilm- K.K.M Jensen, “The Chinese in the Philippines during the American Regime, 1898-1946,” PhD Wisconsin, 1951 (Box 19)
  - Microfilm- Josefa Saniel, “Japan and the Philippines 1868-1898,” PhD UMich, 1961 (Box 19)
  - Microfilm- Gaimusho Documents: survey relating to problems of Phil. Independence, 1924; US-Japan relations, the P.I. problem; Privy Council ratification Jap-Phil treaty; Minutes of Plenary session re J-P treaty; telegrams Jap Amb’s to Min for atf (Box 19)
  - Microfilm- Gaimusho Captured Documents: list of contents and selected translations, 1962 (Box 19)
  - Microfilm- BIA notes on Claike Amend 1916; Indep Missions, 1924, 1958 (Box 19)
  - Microfilm- AMYOT- Chinese in Manila, 1961 (Box 19)
  - Backup disks for The Blue Eyed Enemy, Chapters I through 9 (Box 19)
  - Backup disks for The Blue Eyed Enemy, Chapters 10 through 11, footnotes, notes, chapter outline, bibliographical essay, introduction, and conclusion (Box 19)
  - Student recordings of TWF lectures c. 1962 (three reels), 1962 (Box 19)
  - Spool- Documents, Quezon Collection, 1910-1934 (Items 1-72, Citron Index); I in series of IV (Box 19)
  - Spool- Documents, Quezon Collection, 1910-1934 (Items 73-115, Citron Index); Special Folders, Coll and Misc. no’s 1-5; II in series of IV (Box 19)
  - Spool- Special Folders no’s 5; note cards, alphabetical by topic (subject); note cards, ablph. By source; III in series of IV (Box 19)
  - Spool- Note cards, aph. By source (concluded); IV in series of IV (Box 19)
  - Spool- Manila Microfilms, 1958 (Box 19)
  - Spool- Unlabeled (Box 19)
  - Color Transparencies- James Carr photographs-Thailand and Malaya, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Color Transparencies- James Carr photographs-Manila, Macau, Singapore, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Color Transparencies- James Carr photographs-Bangkok and Thailand, general, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Color Transparencies- James Carr photographs-Thailand rural shots, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Color Transparencies- James Carr photographs-Penang and Malaya, general, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Color Transparencies- Pringle photographs-Angkor 1-20, 1971 (Box 19)
  - Color Transparencies- Pringle photographs- Angkor 21-40, 1971 (Box 19)
  - Color Transparencies- Pringle photographs- Angkor 41-60, 1971 (Box 19)
  - Color Transparencies- Pringle photographs- Thailand, Laos, Cambodia, 1971 (Box 19)
  - Color Transparencies- Lecture 5; Removed for use in SEA Course 1982, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Malaysian currency encased in plastic (Box 19)